Register of the Sir Karl Raimund Popper Papers, 1928-1995
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE I, 1932-1987
  - British Journal for the Philosophy of Science (Ronald F. J. Withers, Mary B. Hesse, John W. N. Watkins, Donald A. Gillies, John Worrall), 1957-1984. (Folder 24)
    Includes correspondence with Raimo H. Tuomela and D. Reidel Publishing Company, as well as John Oultan Wisdom's typewritten "A Statement by the Editor of the BJPS," 1964 May 29. See also Crombie, A. C.
  - British Museum, 1949-1980 (Folder 25)
  - British Society for the Philosophy of Science, 1961-1984 (Folder 26)
  - Broadley, James A., 1980 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Broda, Engelbert, 1976-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Broda, Paul M. A., 1983 (Folder 3)
  - Bronowski, Jacob Bruno (Salk Institute for Biological Studies), 1965-1968 (Folder 4)
  - Brooke-Wavell, Bruce, 1953-1959. (Folder 5)
    Includes correspondence with Evert W. Beth. See also Lejewski, Czeslaw
  - Brookes, Bertram C., 1980 (Folder 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1963 (Folder 7)
  - Brouwer, L. E. J., 1946-1951 (Folder 8)
  - Brun, Georg C., 1985 (Folder 9)
  - Brunner, Fraulein, 1970, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 10)
  - Brunner, Walter, 1983-1985 (Folder 11)
  - Bryant, Ian P., 1976. (Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence with G. Duncan Mitchell
  - Brykman, Genevieve, 1978-1979 (Folder 13)
  - Brynes, Steve, 1976-1977 (Folder 14)
  - Bub, Jeffrey, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Bubke, Otto, 1983 (Folder 16)
  - Buck, Gail, 1976 (Folder 17)
  - Buck, Klaus Markus, 1981-1982, re The Self and Its Brain (Folder 18)
  - Buck, Roger C., 1962 (Folder 19)
  - Budinich, Paolo, 1983 (Folder 20)
  - Budzyner, Simon, 1973-1981 (Folder 21)
  - Buhler, Axel, 1976-1978 (Folder 22)
  - Buller, E. Amy, 1954 (Folder 23)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientist. See Shils, Edward
  - Bundy, A., 1979 (Folder 24)
  - Bunge, Mario
    - 1959-1965 (Folder 25)
    - 1966-1969 (Folder 26)
    - 1970-1982 (Folder 27)
  - Burch, P. R. J., 1976 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Bureau Hongrois pour la Protection des Droits d'Auteur (ARTISJUS), re "Der Positivismus Streit in der deutschen Soziologie", 1972-1973 (Folder 2)
  - Burgess, Tyrrell, 1975-1981 (Folder 3)
  - Burgoyne, Bernard, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Burri, Otto, 1984 (Folder 5)
  - Burstein, Joseph, 1959-1975 (Folder 6)
  - Busch, Friedrich, 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Buske, Herr, 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Butler, Ronald J. (University of Kent at Canterbury), 1971 (Folder 9)
  - Butschek, Felix, 1977 (Folder 10)
  - Buxton, Laurie, 1983 (Folder 11)
  - Byers, P. D., 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Byhovsky, A. V., 1980 (Folder 13)
  - C.H. Beck'sche Verlagsbuchhandlung, 1961-1976 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - C.H. Boehringer Sohn (Julian H. Shelley), 1979-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Cabral, Roque, 1979-1980, re The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 3)
  - Cadevall, Magi, 1984 (Folder 4)
  - Cadogan, Peter, 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Caldin, E. F., 1951 (Folder 6)
  - Calogero, Guido, 1976-1977 (Folder 7)
  - Camber, Bruce Earl, 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Cambridge Moral Science Club, 1946-1953 (Folder 9)
  - Cambridge Union Society (Rajeev Dhavan), 1970 (Folder 10)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1967-1980 (Folder 11)
  - Campbell, Donald T., 1963-1980 (Folder 12)
  - Campbell, E. J. Moran, 1976-1979 (Folder 13-14)
  - Campbell, R. M., 1945 (Folder 15)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1976-1982 (Folder 16)
  - Canijo, Manuel, 1979 (Folder 17)
  - Cantore, Enrico, 1977 (Folder 18)
  - Capek, Milic, 1983-1985 (Folder 19)
  - Carew Hunt, R. N., 1950-1959 (Folder 20)
  - Carl Hanser Verlag, 1982-1984 (Folder 21)
  - Carl Menger Institut, 1985 (Folder 22)
  - Carleton College (Martin Eshleman), 1959-1960. (Folder 23)
    Includes correspondence with Wolfgang Yourgrau
  - Carnap, Rudolf, 1932-1967. (Folder 24)
    Includes typewritten notes by Karl Popper entitled "A Few Remarks on the Introduction to Semantics," as well as letters from Rudolf Carnap's daughter Hanna Thost, 1971
  - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Carr, Brian, 1977 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Carrington, Peter, 1984 (Folder 2)
  - Carr-Saunders, Alexander M., 1962 (Folder 3)
  - Carstens, Karl, 1982 (Folder 4)
  - Carstensen, Hans-Jorgen, 1982 (Folder 5)
  - Carter, John, 1975-1979. (Folder 6)
    Includes correspondence with Ches Crosbie, 1976
  - Carter-Ruck, Peter F., 1975, re Unended Quest (Folder 7)
  - Carvalho, Manoel Joaquim de, Jr., 1977-1985 (Folder 8)
  - Carvalho, Roberto, 1979 (Folder 9)
  - Case, Ron E., 1978 (Folder 10)
  - Casimir, H. B. G., 1981 (Folder 11)
  - Caspar, Norbert, 1978-1979 (Folder 12)
  - Caswell, Hal, 1973-1977 (Folder 13)
  - Catlin, George E. G., 1946-1970. (Folder 14)
    Includes letter from George Catlin to Roy Harrod
  - Caton, Hiram, 1984 (Folder 15)
  - Caws, Peter, 1960-1971. (Folder 16)
    Includes letter from Clifford P. Osborne
  - Cecchini, Arnaldo (DAEST - Istituto Universario di Architettura di Venezia), 1984-1985 (Folder 17)
  - Centenario di Einstein (Francesco de Finis), 1976-1978. (Folder 18)
    Includes correspondence with Beniamino Segre (Accademia Nazionale dei Lincei) and Giunti Publishing Group
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Ralph W. Tyler, Gardner Lindzey), 1956-1976. (Folder 19)
    Includes correspondence re Hans Albert, and with Edgar B. Wesley, H. Kidd, Sydney Caine, Alexander M. Carr-Saunders, and John W. Watkins
  - Centre Europeen de la Culture (Alison Browning), 1979-1980 (Folder 20)
  - Centre Europeen de Recherche Nucleaire (R. Hagedorn), See also Aichelburg, P., 1977-1979. (Folder 21)
  - Centre Royaumont pour une Science de l'Homme, 1975-1976. (Folder 22)
    Includes conversation notes
  - Centro di Ricerca e Documentazione "Luigi Einaudi" (Giuliano Urbani), 1980 (Folder 23)
  - Centro Studi e Ricerche su Problemi Economico-Sociali (Dario Staffa), 1973-1974 (Folder 24)
  - Centro Superiore di Logica e Scienze Comparate (Franco Spisani), 1971-1974 (Folder 25)
  - Cerovic, Stanko, 1982 (Folder 26)
  - Chalfont, Lord, 1984 (Folder 27)
  - Challis, Christine, 1985 (Folder 28)
  - Chalmes, Iain, 1982 (Folder 29)
  - Chamberlin, Raymond A., 1983 (Folder 30)
  - Chambers, 1955 (Folder 31)
  - Champion, Ralph A., 1971-1986 (Folder 32)
  - Chandrasekhar, Subrahmanian, 1977 (Folder 33)
  - Chapman, P. D. H., 1973 (Folder 34)
  - Charlton, Nial, 1981 (Folder 35)
  - Chattopadhyay, D. P. (Debi Prasad), 1961-1983 (Folder 36)
  - Chaudhury, Mahasweta, 1981-1986 (Folder 37)
  - Chedzey, Clifford, 1978 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Chelsea College, 1969-1984 (Folder 2)
  - Cherniss, Harold, 1958-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Cherry, E. Colin, 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences. See British Academy
  - Chinnappa, Nanjamma, 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Chmielewski, Adam, 1982-1985 (Folder 6)
  - Chokr, Nader, 1984 (Folder 7)
  - Choynowski, Mieyczyslaw, 1947 (Folder 8)
  - Christian, Curt, 1983 (Folder 9)
  - Chroust, Anton-Hermann ( Natural Law Forum ), 1958-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Chudnovsky, David, re Andrei Sakharov, 1981 (Folder 11)
  - Church, Alonzo, 1947-1948 (Folder 12)
  - Church, Joseph, 1966 (Folder 13)
  - Churchill, Winston, the Younger, 1971-1973 (Folder 14)
  - Cioffi, Frank, 1952-1953 (Folder 15)
  - City University, London, 1976-1983 (Folder 16)
  - Civitas. See Gesellschaft zur Forderung von Wissenschaft und Kunst
  - Claassen, Emil, 1966 (Folder 17)
  - Clapp, Roger E., 1981 (Folder 18)
  - Clare Market Review, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - Clarendon Press (Adam Hodgkin, Nicholas Wilson), 1971-1981, re Objective Knowledge. (Folder 20)
    Includes blurbs, corrected galleys, and notes
  - Clark, Peter, 1974 (Folder 21)
  - Clark, Ronald W., 1985 (Folder 22)
  - Clarke, John J., 1982 (Folder 23)
  - Clarkson, Geoffrey P. E., 1973 (Folder 24)
  - Clauser, John F., 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Cleary, John J., 1975-1982 (Folder 26)
  - Cleve, Felix M., 1982-1983 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Clontz, Jack M., 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Club Turati (Riccardo Viale), 1982. (Folder 3)
    Includes letters from W. H. Newton-Smith
  - Cochrane, A. L., 1982 (Folder 4)
  - Cohen, H. F., 1984 (Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Kalman Joseph, 1953-1954 (Folder 6)
  - Cohen, L. Jonathan, 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Robert S., 1965-1981 (Folder 8)
  - Cohen of Birkenhead, Lord, 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Cohn, Melvin, re Jacques Monod, 1976 (Folder 10)
  - Coing, Helmut, 1982-1985 (Folder 11)
  - Coleman, Sam, 1964 (Folder 12)
  - Coles, James S., 1966-1968 (Folder 13)
  - Coles, Norman, 1984 (Folder 14)
  - College of Advanced Technology, 1961 (Folder 15)
  - College Psychiatrique de Recherches en Epistemologie Popperienne (Claude-Jacques Blanc), 1982 (Folder 16)
  - Collier, Barbara, 1975 (Folder 17)
  - Collier Macmillan International, 1968-1976 (Folder 18)
  - Collins (Publisher), 1981 (Folder 19)
  - Collins, Kins, 1967-1970. (Folder 20)
    Includes correspondence re Conjectures and Refutations
  - Collins, Warwick, 1975 (Folder 21)
  - Colston Research Society, 1984 (Folder 22)
  - Commentary, 1952 (Folder 23)
  - Commission of the European Communities (Mark F. Cantley), 1984 (Folder 24)
  - Committee for the Free World. See Labedz, Leopold
  - Comparetti, Adriano Milani, 1982 (Folder 25)
  - Complexe (Andre Versaille), 1975, re Der Positivismusstreit in der deutschen Soziologie (Folder 26)
  - Compton, John J. and Betty, 1965-1969 (Folder 27)
  - Conceptus: Zeitschrift fur Philosophie (Helmut Kasper, Johann Christian Marek), 1968-1977. (Folder 28)
    Includes correspondence with Hans Lenk
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion (Ordway Tead), 1952 (Folder 29)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom. See Kongress fur die Freiheit der Kultur
  - Conner, Daniel K., 1972 (Folder 30)
  - Conrad, Alfred H., 1963 (Folder 31)
  - Constantin, Yves de, n.d. (Folder 32)
  - Continuum Books, 1974 (Folder 33)
  - Cook, Norman D., 1974 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Cooke, Joseph J., 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Cooperman, David, 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Copi, Irving M., 1963-1965 (Folder 4)
  - Corson, David, 1983 (Folder 5)
  - Costa, Joaquim da, 1980 (Folder 6)
  - Costa de Beauregard, O., 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Council for Science and Society (Kenneth Denbigh), 1974-1982 (Folder 8)
  - Council of Europe, 1983-1984 (Folder 9)
  - Craig, William, 1960-1962 (Folder 10)
  - Cramer, John G., 1982 (Folder 11)
  - Cranberg, Lawrence, 1979-1982 (Folder 12)
  - Crane, R. S., 1961 (Folder 13)
  - Cranston, Maurice, 1951-1975 (Folder 14)
  - Creed, Walter G., 1976-1981 (Folder 15)
  - Creutzfeldt, Otto, 1983 (Folder 16)
  - Crewe, Sabrina, 1983 (Folder 17)
  - Crick, Francis H. C., 1982 (Folder 18)
  - Crombie, Alistair C., 1948-1977 (Folder 19)
  - Crombie, David L., 1963-1970 (Folder 20)
  - Croom Helm Publishers, 1984 (Folder 21)
  - Crossman, R. H. S., 1959 (Folder 22)
  - Cubeddu, Raimondo, 1978-1980 (Folder 23)
  - Cunha, A. Brito da, 1973-1979 (Folder 24)
  - Cunningham, Robert L., re Friedrich A. von Hayek, 1975 (Folder 25)
  - Current Affairs, 1973 (Folder 26)
  - Currie, Gregory, 1977-1982 (Folder 27)
  - Cutting, James E., 1978 (Folder 28)
  - Cysarz, Herbert, 1971 (Folder 29)
  - Czayka, Lothar, 1975 (Folder 30)
  - DAIS, 1967, re The Logic of Scientific Discovery (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1975-1985. (Folder 2)
    Includes letter from Gino Tarozzi
  - Dahlberg, Ingetraut, 1974 (Folder 3)
  - Dahlstrom, Hans, 1979-1980 (Folder 4)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralf, 1961-1984 (Folder 5)
  - Dalai Lama, The, 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Dalziel, E. M. and Margaret, 1958-1984 (Folder 7)
  - Daney, John and Angela (Marlborough College), 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Danielian, A., 1982 (Folder 9)
  - Daniels, Charles B., 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Danielsen, Niels, 1972-1980 (Folder 11)
  - Danish Society for Philosophy and Psychology, 1962 (Folder 12)
  - Danzig, Professor, 1946 (Folder 13)
  - Darlington, Cyril D., 1970 (Folder 14)
  - Darmstadter Blatter, 1983 (Folder 15)
  - Darwin College (Moses I. Finley, John Butterfield), 1980-1985. (Folder 16)
    Includes notes on Charles Darwin by Karl Popper, and correspondence with the Darwin Centenary Conference, 27 June-2 July 1982 (D. H. Mellor)
  - Daskalakis, George D., 1966 (Folder 17)
  - Davies, David, 1985 (Folder 18)
  - Davies, John T., 1952-1979 (Folder 19)
  - Davis, Philip J., 1978 (Folder 20)
  - Davis, Quintin V., 1975-1976 (Folder 21)
  - Dawe, Peter G. M., 1951-1980 (Folder 22)
  - Dawkins, Richard, 1982 (Folder 23)
  - Deinhardt, Friedrich, 1980 (Folder 24)
  - Del-Negro, Walter von, 1981 (Folder 25)
  - Dell, Paul, 1976 (Folder 26)
  - Dellian, Ed, 1984 (Folder 27)
  - Deltgen, Florian, 1968-1969 (Folder 28)
  - Dembeck, Richard C., 1961 (Folder 29)
  - Demers, Pierre, 1971 (Folder 30)
  - Denbigh, Kenneth, 1976-1983 (Folder 31)
  - Denker, Rolf, 1977 (Folder 32)
  - Dennett, Professor, 1977 (Folder 33)
  - Department of Scientific and Industrial Research (A. P. J. Edwards), 1961 (Folder 34)
  - Derrick, John, 1966 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Destopoulos, Constantin, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Deutsch, David, 1977-1984 (Folder 3)
  - Deutsch, Gitta, 1983 (Folder 4)
  - Deutsche Akademie fur Sprache und Dichtung, 1979-1985 (Folder 5)
  - Deutsche Rundschau (Harry Pross), 1959-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Deutsche Schule London (Friedrich Denk), re Friedrich Durrenmatt, 1985 (Folder 7)
  - Deutsche Universitatszeitung, 1958 (Folder 8)
  - Deutsche Verlags-Anstalt (Wolfram Huncke), 1979, re The Self and Its Brain (Folder 9)
  - Deutscher Taschenbuch Verlag (Walter Kumpmann, Renate Schwalb), 1974-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Deutsches Institut fur Wissenschaftliche Padagogik, 1975-1976 (Folder 11)
  - Devaux, Philippe, 1967-1978. (Folder 12)
    Includes letter to Mrs. Devaux, 1983
  - De Vries, G. J., n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Dialectica (Henri Lauener), 1970-1983. (Folder 14)
    Includes notes and correspondence with Duen Marti-Huang, 1984
  - Diamond, R. J., 1962-1972 (Folder 15)
  - Dictionary of the History of Ideas (Philip P. Wiener, Charles E. Pettee), 1967-1970 (Folder 16)
  - Dilia (G. Bernau), 1968 (Folder 17)
  - Dilworth, R. P., 1968 (Folder 18)
  - Dimitrakos, Dimitri N., 1981-1984 (Folder 19)
  - Dinges, Hermann, 1979 (Folder 20)
  - Dingle, Herbert, 1960-1974 (Folder 21)
  - Dion, Leon, 1951 (Folder 22)
  - Discover (Lois Wingerson), 1981-1982 (Folder 23)
  - Disselbeck, Klaus, 1983-1984 (Folder 24)
  - Ditchfield, Robert, 1972 (Folder 25)
  - Ditfurth, Hoimar von, 1974-1979 (Folder 26)
  - Diverse, 1984 (Folder 27)
  - Dixon, Michael ( Financial Times ), 1978 (Folder 28)
  - Djilas, Milovan, 1977 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Djuric, Mihailo, 1959-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Doderlein, Jan M. (Royal Norwegian Council for Scientific and Industrial Research), 1975-1981 (Folder 3)
  - Dokumentationsarchiv des Osterreichischen Widerstandes, 1982 (Folder 4)
  - Dolby, James L., 1983 (Folder 5)
  - Dombrowski, Daniel A., 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Dombrowski, Heinz Dieter, 1970 (Folder 7)
  - Donagan, Alan, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Donaldson, Mrs. Howard M., 1950 (Folder 9)
  - Doring, Eberhard, 1978-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Doubleday, 1978-1979 (Folder 11)
  - Doucet, L., 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Dover Publications, 1959 (Folder 13)
  - Drachman, G., 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Dray, William, 1982 (Folder 15)
  - Dreksler, Jacob J., 1970-1971 (Folder 16)
  - Drew, Philip, 1982 (Folder 17)
  - Dreyers Forlag, 1981-1982 (Folder 18)
  - Driver, Alan, 1981-1985 (Folder 19)
  - Dub, Otto, 1972 (Folder 20)
  - Duckworth (General Publishers), 1977 (Folder 21)
  - Duda, Elisabeth, 1978-1985 (Folder 22)
  - Duerr, Hans Peter, 1979-1980 (Folder 23)
  - Duftner, Carin. See Moser-Duftner, Carin
  - Dulwich College Science Society (Nicholas Gough), 1984 (Folder 24)
  - Duncan-Jones, Austin, 1954, re Die Logik der Forschung (Folder 25)
  - Duncker & Humblot, 1965-1983 (Folder 26)
  - Dunn, Michael (and Geoffrey Hellman), 1985 (Folder 27)
  - Dunnwald, Marianne, 1964 (Folder 28)
  - Dunsire, Andrew, 1981 (Folder 29)
  - Durr, Karl, 1947-1949 (Folder 30)
  - Duschek, Adalbert, 1950 (Folder 31)
  - E.P. Dutton, 1959 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Early Music, 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Ebbinghaus, Julius, 1968-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Ebert, Theodor, 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Ebringer, Alan, 1983 (Folder 5)
  - Eccles, John Carew.
    Includes correspondence and notes re The Self and Its Brain, and correspondence with Mouton Publishers and Springer Verlag
    - Undated. (Folder 6)
      Includes Karl Popper's handwritten and typewritten comments on John C. Eccles' paper "An Electrical Hypothesis of Synaptic and Neuro-Muscular Transmission"
    - 1945-1949 (Folder 7)
    - 1950-1959 (Folder 8)
    - 1961-1969 (Folder 9)
    - 1970-1974 (Folder 10)
    - 1975 (Folder 11)
    - 1976-1977 (Folder 12)
    - 1978 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - 1979-1984 (Folder 2)
  - Economica, 1979 (Folder 3)
  - Edelman, Gerald M., 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Edgerton, Stephenie G., 1965-1984 (Folder 5)
  - Ediciones Paidos Iberica, 1983-1984, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 6)
  - Edicoes Roger Delraux, 1978, re The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 7)
  - Edition Tusch (Kristian Sotriffer), 1980 (Folder 8)
  - Editions Calmann-Levy (Robert Calmann-Levy, Alain Oulman, Therese Scaroni, Christian Schmidt), 1979-1982, re Unended Quest (Folder 9)
  - Editions Complexe (Andre Versaille), 1978-1981, re Objective Knowledge (Folder 10)
  - Editions du Seuil (Paul Flamand, Francois Wahl, Jean-Marc Levy-Leblond), 1972-1981, re The Open Society and Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 11)
  - Editions Gallimard (Pierre Nora), 1978-1980 (Folder 12)
  - Editions Magnard, 1979 (Folder 13)
  - Editions Payot (Catherine Alicot, Jean-Luc Pidoux-Payot), 1979-1985, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 14)
  - Editora Cultrix (Diaulas Riedel), 1977-1983, re The Poverty of Historicism and Unended Quest (Folder 15)
  - Editore Armando Armando, 1971-1977, re Unended Quest, Epistemology Without a Knowing Subject, and Of Clouds and Clocks. (Folder 16)
    Includes correspondence with Arcangelo Rossi re Objective Knowledge, and with Bryan Magee and Midland Bank
  - Editorial Paidos, 1968-1970, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 17)
  - Editorial Perfil, 1977 (Folder 18)
  - Editorial Planeta, 1982 (Folder 19)
  - Editorial Tecnos (Gabriel Tortella Oteo, Alejandro Sierra Benayas), 1975-1984, re The Logic of Scientific Discovery, Unended Quest, and The Open Universe (Folder 20)
  - Editura Stiintifica si Enciclopedica, 1974-1981, re The Logic of Scientific Discovery (Folder 21)
  - Edizioni Borla (Vincenzo D'Agostino), 1981, re Die beiden Grundprobleme der Erkenntnisstheorie (Folder 22)
  - Edizioni della Nuova Antologia (Riccardo Campa), re "The Moral Responsibility of the Scientist.", 1969-1974 (Folder 23)
    Includes Italian typewritten translation
  - Edson, L. L., 1945 (Folder 24)
  - Edwards, J. S., 1976 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Edwards, M. J., 1979-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Edwards, Paul ( Encyclopedia of Philosophy ), 1965-1984 (Folder 3)
  - Edwards, Ronald S., 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Egydio Martins(?), Lila B., 1980 (Folder 5)
  - Ehlers, Jurgen, 1984 (Folder 6)
  - Ehrenhaft, Felix, 1949 (Folder 7)
  - Ehrenkreutz, A. S., 1951 (Folder 8)
  - Eibl-Eibesfeldt, Irenaus, 1985 (Folder 9)
  - Eidlin, Fred H., 1977-1985 (Folder 10)
  - Eilers, Wolfgang, 1984 (Folder 11)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1935. (Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence with John Stachel (Einstein Project), 1977-1984.See also Estate of Albert Einstein
  - Eisler, Robert and Lili, 1946-1972 (Folder 13)
  - Elders, Fons, 1974 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Ellinghouse, M. P., 1978 (Folder 2)
  - Ellington, H. I., 1977-1979 (Folder 3)
  - Ellis, Bob, 1973-1974 (Folder 4)
  - Ellis, Weldon, 1984 (Folder 5)
  - Elvee, Richard Quentin (Gustavus Adolphus College), 1980-1982 (Folder 6)
  - Emmet, Dorothy M., 1946-1979 (Folder 7)
  - Emory University (Judson C. Ward, Jr.), 1969-1970 (Folder 8)
  - Encounter (Irving Kristol, Melvin J. Lasky, Bryan Healing), 1955-1979 (Folder 9)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1963-1975 (Folder 10)
  - Engel, Friedrich, 1948 (Folder 11)
  - Engelbrecht, Chris A., 1982 (Folder 12)
  - Engelhorn, Peter, 1984 (Folder 13)
  - Engl, Max C., 1982 (Folder 14)
  - Epidemiology Resources (Stephen F. Lanes), 1985 (Folder 15)
  - Epoca, 1984 (Folder 16)
  - Erasmus (Rudolf Jud), 1979 (Folder 17)
  - Erfahrung und Denken (Kurt Schelldorfer), 1955-1966, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 18)
  - Ergo, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Erhard, Werner, 1981-1982. (Folder 20)
    Includes letter from Polly Lansdowne
  - Ernst Klett Verlag, 1983 (Folder 21)
  - Eschbach, Achim, 1981-1983 (Folder 22)
  - Estate of Albert Einstein (Otto Nathan), 1956 (Folder 23)
  - Et Cetera (Paul Levinson), 1976-1978 (Folder 24)
  - Etges, Peter J., 1973, re Objective Knowledge. (Folder 25)
    Includes corrections to the index
  - Eucken, Rudolf Christoph, 1984 (Folder 26)
  - Eucken-Erdsiek, Edith, 1966 (Folder 27)
  - Eugen Rentsch Verlag, 1946, re The Open Society (Folder 28)
  - Euler, Hans, 1935 (Folder 29)
  - Europa Verlag (Emmie Oprecht), 1960-1962 (Folder 30)
  - Evans, Charles, 1978 (Folder 31)
  - Evans, Eve, 1949-1954 (Folder 32)
  - Evans, Ifor, 1960 (Folder 33)
  - Evans, J. L., 1954 (Folder 34)
  - Evans-Pritchard, E. E., 1957 (Folder 35)
  - Ewer, Jonathan and Sally, 1979 (Folder 36)
  - Ewing, A. C., 1946 (Folder 37)
  - Express (Sophie Lannes), 1981 (Folder 38)
  - Eysenck, H. J., 1978 (Folder 39)
  - Faludi, Andreas, 1981-1983 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Farrelly, R. J., 1977 (Folder 2)
  - Faure, Edgar, 1981-1984 (Folder 3)
  - Fauth, Wilfried, 1982-1984 (Folder 4)
  - Federation Internationale des Societes de Philosophie (Andre Mercier), 1972-1975 (Folder 5)
  - Feigl, Herbert and Maria, 1945-1978 (Folder 6)
  - Felchtinger, Frieda, 1962 (Folder 7)
  - Fernandez de Soto, Leon, 1982 (Folder 8)
  - Fernsehen der Deutschen und der Ratoromanischen Schweiz, 1982-1984. (Folder 9)
  - Ferretto, Alessandro, 1974-1975 (Folder 10)
  - Fetzer, James H., 1967-1982 (Folder 11)
  - Feuer, Lewis S., 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Feyerabend, Paul K.
    - Undated (Folder 13)
    - 1949 (Folder 14)
    - 1953 (Folder 15)
    - 1954 (Folder 16)
    - 1955 (Folder 17)
    - 1956 (Folder 18)
    - 1957 (Folder 19)
    - 1958 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - 1959 (Folder 2)
    - 1960 (Folder 3)
    - 1961 (Folder 4)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 5)
    - 1965 (Folder 6)
    - 1966 (Folder 7)
    - 1967 (Folder 8)
  - Fiedler, Harald, 1983 (Folder 9)
  - Fields, Harvey and Janet (Folder 10)
  - Fillencz, Marianne, 1947-1984 (Folder 11)
  - Finch, Henry A., 1960 (Folder 12)
  - Findlay, Allan F., 1960-1968 (Folder 13)
  - Findlay, John N., 1939-1968 (Folder 14)
  - Finkelstein, David, 1968 (Folder 15)
  - Firnberg, Herta, 1976-1984 (Folder 16)
  - Firneis, Friedrich, 1982 (Folder 17)
  - Fischer, E. Hugo, 1970 (Folder 18)
  - Fischer, Gerhard, 1984 (Folder 19)
  - Fischer, J. L., 1970 (Folder 20)
  - Fischer, Wolfram, 1968 (Folder 21)
  - Fisher, George, 1978 (Folder 22)
  - Fisher, Gordon, 1978 (Folder 23)
  - Fissenewert, Horst and Christiane (Fissenewert-Kilthau), 1981 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Fleischmann, Bernd, 1984 (Folder 2)
  - Fleischmann, Charlotte, 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Fleischmann, Gerd and Ingeborg, 1961-1984. (Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence re Objective Knowledge and Unended Quest, as well as a holograph fragment by Karl Popper
  - Flew, Antony G. N., 1973-1985 (Folder 5)
  - Flieder-Trio, 1978-1979 (Folder 6)
  - Foldes, Lucien P., 1966 (Folder 7)
  - Fondamenti, 1984 (Folder 8)
  - Fondation Louis de Broglie, 1981-1983 (Folder 9)
  - Fondazione Luigi Einaudi, 1982 (Folder 10)
  - Fondul Literar al Scriitorilor Din, 1981 (Folder 11)
  - Fontana Paperbacks (Helen Fraser, Alison Wade, Robert B. Woodings), 1975-1984, re Unended Quest. (Folder 12)
    Includes typewritten blurbs for A Pocket Popper
  - Ford, G. W., 1948 (Folder 13)
  - Ford, Oliver E., 1965-1974. (Folder 14)
  - Forder, H. G., 1943-1945 (Folder 15)
  - Forlaget Akademilitteratur, 1982 (Folder 16)